we've been given
two variables array one and array two
each referencing a three element array
we need to compare these two arrays and
print true or false based on whether
they match
so we can perform a simple comparison
and this equality comparison will return
a boolean either true or false
so all we need to do to print true or
false
is to output the return value of this
comparison
so let's invoke put s and the return
value of this comparison will be the
argument passed to put us
we've output false
the two arrays that we were comparing
have the same number of elements
and in fact they include these same
three integers as
elements but the order of these elements
doesn't match
let's see what would happen to our
comparison if it did
now each array has the elements 1
5 and 9 in that order
running our code again this time the
comparison returns true
so these two arrays will be seen as
equal
if their elements match
if they contain the same elements in a
different order
we see that inequality comparison
returns false
you